Paul Marrable

Web Developer

e: paul.marrable@plinx-tech.co.uk w: www.paulmarrable.co.uk m: 07824 366376

Personal Profile

I am currently a full stack developer for the live services department at Codemasters in Southam. I also run an independent video game studio called Flump Studios.

I have been developing software and games for over 25 years and I have maintained a strong passion for software development, with the art of clean coding being of particular interest. Over the years I have gained experience developing with C#, C++, Javascript, Typescript, Python, VB, Lua, Unity 3D, HTML, CSS, SASS, AngularJS, ReactJS, ASP.Net, SQL and various other languages and frameworks.

As a web developer, my current preferred stack is C#.Net Core 3+, Entity FW core and ReactJS with Redux.

Work Experience

Full stack web developer

Jan 2020- Present

My role at Codemasters has proven to be more varied than my previous roles and has me jumping from web API and app development to game server development, from architecting large projects and databases to client side coding and even the occasional desktop app. I use a range of technology and stacks at Codemasters, but the majority of my time is spent with .NET core 3.1, MSSQL and ReactJS

Full stack web developer

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

API, Web app and website design and development. Currently leading the development of a web API and SPA data store project using .NET Core 2+, React with redux, and MSsqI with Entity FW core.

Full stack web developer

Apr 2016 - Jan 2019

Web app, API, website design and development. Working primarily with C# .NET and .NET Core, React, AngularJs, Umbraco and MSsql with Entity FW Core and ADO.

Video Game Developer

Jan 2011 - present

Design and developerment of independent video games, both solo and part of a small team. For my more recent projects I have been using Unity3D with C#, moving over from C# with XNA/Monogame to aid development speed. For many years Flump Studios was my full time job, until my first son was born and decided I needed something more stable.

Key Skills

C#
.NET Core
React JS
Typescript
HTML/CSS/JS
SQL/Entity Framework
TDD
GIT
Agile

Education

Uxbridge College 09/1997 - 07/2000 GNVQ in IT BTEC National Diploma in Computer studies